[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "ORGAN: Did you think one day you'd be world famous for cross- dressing?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "think", "one", "day", "you", "'d", "be", "world", "famous", "for", "cross-", "dressing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "It's all going to plan?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "going", "to", "plan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "You know, when the votes started getting counted we knew pretty quickly we have -- you know, we have a fairly sophisticated model.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "when", "the", "votes", "started", "getting", "counted", "we", "knew", "pretty", "quickly", "we", "have", "--", "you", "know", ",", "we", "have", "a", "fairly", "sophisticated", "model", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Were you pleased about the level of the turnout?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "pleased", "about", "the", "level", "of", "the", "turnout", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "If you were putting your strategist's hat on and looking at their campaign, where do you think they really, in the end, lost it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "putting", "your", "strategist", "'s", "hat", "on", "and", "looking", "at", "their", "campaign", ",", "where", "do", "you", "think", "they", "really", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "lost", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Look, I think the problem for the Republican Party is that the center of gravity has shifted so far to the right that they're way out of the mainstream.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "the", "problem", "for", "the", "Republican", "Party", "is", "that", "the", "center", "of", "gravity", "has", "shifted", "so", "far", "to", "the", "right", "that", "they", "'re", "way", "out", "of", "the", "mainstream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "But how much of the responsibility lies with him, with Speaker Boehner, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "much", "of", "the", "responsibility", "lies", "with", "him", ",", "with", "Speaker", "Boehner", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I think that he certainly bears some -- people want cooperation on both sides.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "he", "certainly", "bears", "some", "--", "people", "want", "cooperation", "on", "both", "sides", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Are you hoping you're going to get the kind of economic security if not prosperity in this term that will allow you to do perhaps the things Barack Obama, when he sailed in on hope and change, hoped he could do?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "hoping", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "the", "kind", "of", "economic", "security", "if", "not", "prosperity", "in", "this", "term", "that", "will", "allow", "you", "to", "do", "perhaps", "the", "things", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "when", "he", "sailed", "in", "on", "hope", "and", "change", ",", "hoped", "he", "could", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe the economy is improving, but I want to challenge a bit of your premise because one of the reasons the economy is improving is because this president was brave.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "believe", "the", "economy", "is", "improving", ",", "but", "I", "want", "to", "challenge", "a", "bit", "of", "your", "premise", "because", "one", "of", "the", "reasons", "the", "economy", "is", "improving", "is", "because", "this", "president", "was", "brave", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "One is, I understand that the first person the president called after knowing that he won was Bill Clinton, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["One", "is", ",", "I", "understand", "that", "the", "first", "person", "the", "president", "called", "after", "knowing", "that", "he", "won", "was", "Bill", "Clinton", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Does he feel a big debt of gratitude to him?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "feel", "a", "big", "debt", "of", "gratitude", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, there's no question about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Are you a relieved man this morning?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "relieved", "man", "this", "morning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I know this has been the subject of a lot of discussion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "this", "has", "been", "the", "subject", "of", "a", "lot", "of", "discussion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "He's been abused?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "been", "abused", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Abused his entire life.", "answer_tokens": ["Abused", "his", "entire", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 159, "question": "How did you find this out?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "find", "this", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "found", "it", "out", "by", "asking", "questions", ",", "finally", ",", "of", "him", ",", "because", "I", "was", "talking", "to", "him", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "So he told you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "told", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "told", "me", "a", "lot", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "alive", ",", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "'s", "still", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "kind", "of", "relationship", "do", "you", "have", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "speak", "very", "much", ",", "but", "I", "am", "taking", "care", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "You support him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "support", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "despite", "the", "way", "that", "he", "manhandled", "you", "and", "beat", "you", "and", "so", "on", ",", "did", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "loved", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "No, I never felt that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "felt", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "So that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "that", "was", "another", "thing", "I", "did", "n't", "know", ",", "which", "caused", "a", "lot", "of", "issues", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "that", "out", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I did, about four years ago I asked, why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "about", "four", "years", "ago", "I", "asked", ",", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Is that guilt, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "guilt", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Every award -- and listen, that's exactly what I thought very early on.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "award", "--", "and", "listen", ",", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "I", "thought", "very", "early", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "ever", "said", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "No, he hasn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "has", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Would you like him to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "point", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "it", "matters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "question_tokens": ["She", "--", "it", "--", "well", ",", "you", "mean", "of", "all", "the", "success", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "question_tokens": ["--", "get", "her", "a", "red", "Jaguar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Jaguar"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "--", "she", "'s", "speechless", ",", "just", "a", "thank", "you", "and", "the", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "talking", "to", ",", "old", "lady", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "You don't know me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "know", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Did you ever think when you were young and you started treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross- dressing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "think", "when", "you", "were", "young", "and", "you", "started", "treading", "the", "boards", "that", "one", "day", "you", "'d", "be", "world", "famous", "for", "cross-", "dressing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes, never --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "never", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "lots", "of", "other", "Madeas", "from", "every", "--", "I", "'ve", "met", "a", "Jewish", "Madea", ",", "I", "'ve", "met", "an", "Italian", "Madea", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "It's about strong women.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "strong", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Any comment?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "comment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "question_tokens": ["You", "feel", "uncomfortable", "talking", "about", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "try", "--", "it", "drives", "me", "insane", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "-- show off about it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "show", "off", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "who", "wants", "to", "show", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "certainly", "not", "about", "showing", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "thing", "about", "money", ",", "though", ",", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "the", "best", "thing", "which", "is", "--", "which", "changed", "my", "entire", "life", "was", "being", "able", "to", "support", "my", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "--", "why", "do", "you", "feel", "awkward", "talking", "about", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, because it's -- I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "just", "feel", "that", "to", "whom", "much", "is", "given", ",", "much", "is", "required", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "avoided", "the", "pitfalls", "that", "go", "with", "superstar", "fame", ",", "big", "money", "and", "all", "the", "rest", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "My faith.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "faith", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "It doesn't mean that order?", "question_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "mean", "that", "order", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "In that order.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "that", "order", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "enjoy", "playing", "the", "action", "hero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I actually did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "You've lost 30 pounds?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "lost", "30", "pounds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Golston"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "How did you do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Mostly I worked with a trainer, a guy Anthony Golston.", "answer_tokens": ["Mostly", "I", "worked", "with", "a", "trainer", ",", "a", "guy", "Anthony", "Golston", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Krav Maga"], "LOCATION": ["Atlanta"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "But is it basically about you just don't eat as much?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "basically", "about", "you", "just", "do", "n't", "eat", "as", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Yes, you don't -- you don't eat as much and you move a lot more, and the thing that I was working out and running five miles -- this Krav Maga, Israeli fighting, and I'm tell you, I'm dropping names here, but this guy Eric down in Atlanta who worked with me was amazing at -- I did it for five minutes and couldn't get off the floor.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "do", "n't", "eat", "as", "much", "and", "you", "move", "a", "lot", "more", ",", "and", "the", "thing", "that", "I", "was", "working", "out", "and", "running", "five", "miles", "--", "this", "Krav", "Maga", ",", "Israeli", "fighting", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "'m", "dropping", "names", "here", ",", "but", "this", "guy", "Eric", "down", "in", "Atlanta", "who", "worked", "with", "me", "was", "amazing", "at", "--", "I", "did", "it", "for", "five", "minutes", "and", "could", "n't", "get", "off", "the", "floor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Because there are --", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "there", "are", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Once, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "And what went wrong?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "went", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I think we were both very young.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "were", "both", "very", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "It was, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "your", "decision", "to", "walk", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "question_tokens": ["You", "thought", "it", "was", "the", "right", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes, because we both were in a place where -- and I just realized I should not have said this because -- I should not have said this.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "we", "both", "were", "in", "a", "place", "where", "--", "and", "I", "just", "realized", "I", "should", "not", "have", "said", "this", "because", "--", "I", "should", "not", "have", "said", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "n't", "you", "have", "said", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Because I said too much.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "said", "too", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Why don't you ask another question?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "ask", "another", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "This is a fascinating side to you, because you're being so nice about it and so honest.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "fascinating", "side", "to", "you", ",", "because", "you", "'re", "being", "so", "nice", "about", "it", "and", "so", "honest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And what's the rush?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "'s", "the", "rush", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "But don't you want little Tylers running around?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "n't", "you", "want", "little", "Tylers", "running", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Shall we move on?", "question_tokens": ["Shall", "we", "move", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Yes, please.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "please", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Do you want to have a glass of water?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "have", "a", "glass", "of", "water", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "No, I felt good.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "felt", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "No, no, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Did you have any idea who she was?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "idea", "who", "she", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "To be honest with you, I did not.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "be", "honest", "with", "you", ",", "I", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "You've never heard of her?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "never", "heard", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I have heard of her, but I didn't know all of that she had done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "heard", "of", "her", ",", "but", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "all", "of", "that", "she", "had", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "everything", ",", "Tyler", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "Because you supplied the plane, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "supplied", "the", "plane", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Do you believe that the candidates whoever wins the presidency should be doing more to bring in tougher gun control?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "the", "candidates", "whoever", "wins", "the", "presidency", "should", "be", "doing", "more", "to", "bring", "in", "tougher", "gun", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "I mean who's going to take on the gun lobby here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "take", "on", "the", "gun", "lobby", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 800, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 801, "answer": "ERRY: No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["ERRY", ":", "No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "First black bond?", "question_tokens": ["First", "black", "bond", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Will Smith"]}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Why should it be him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "it", "be", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Because if you lose weight at the rate you're going, you'll be skinnier than Will Smith.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "if", "you", "lose", "weight", "at", "the", "rate", "you", "'re", "going", ",", "you", "'ll", "be", "skinnier", "than", "Will", "Smith", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "What would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "There's one moment I'll -- and I will probably regret it for my entire life my mother was -- on a death bed.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "one", "moment", "I", "'ll", "--", "and", "I", "will", "probably", "regret", "it", "for", "my", "entire", "life", "my", "mother", "was", "--", "on", "a", "death", "bed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]